Crone, Michelle; Papers apap101
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Events and Productions, 1982-1996, Undated; 2; 10.1 cubic ft.
  - Festivals - Other, 1982-1996, Undated; 2.7; 0.2 cubic ft.
    - Gilded Age Film Workshop, 1994 (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 40)
    - North East Women's Musical Retreat, 1984-1988 (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 41)
    - North Hampton Lesbian Festival, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 42)
    - Old Songs Festival Traditional Music and Dance - Name tags, Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 43)
    - Southern Women's Music and Comedy Festival, 1984-1991; Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 44)
    - T- shirt - Book Fest of the Palm Beaches: A Literary Festival, 1991 (Box 22 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 5)
    - T-shirt - New England Women's Musical Retreat, North Stonington, Connecticut, 1982 (Oversized 8, Folder 4)
    - West Coast Women's Music and Comedy Festival, 1982-1990; Undated (Box 11 (2-Events and Productions), Folder 45)
- Personal, 1968-1996, Undated; 3; 1 cubic ft.
  This series primarily consists of personal correspondence between Michelle Crone and her friends and personal acquaintances. Crone’s personal life often overlapped with her professional and political life, and thus, many letters discuss topics from other series. Postcards and greeting cards were retained only when they possessed informational content. Additionally, the “Resumes” folder contains several version of Crone’s resume, documenting a number of events and activities that she was involved with until 1996.
  - Correspondence, 1972; 1977; 1980 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 62)
  - Correspondence - Susan Chast, 1981-1991; Undated (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 63)
  - Correspondence - Michael DeMarco, Newspaper Clippings, 1968; Undated (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 64)
  - Correspondence - Mauve, 1990; 1992; 1994; Undated (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 65)
  - Correspondence - Mother, Undated (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 66)
  - Correspondence - Punk, Undated (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 67)
  - Correspondence - Reggae, 1984-1987; 1991; Undated (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 68)
  - Correspondence - Woody Blue, 1985-1987; 1991; Undated (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 69)
  - Crone Performance Flyers, 1991; Undated (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 70)
  - Draft of Will, 1986 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 71)
  - Greeting Cards, 1977-1985 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 72)
  - Greeting Cards, 1985-1989 (Box 11 (3-Personal), Folder 73)
  - Greeting Cards, 1990-1995 (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 1)
  - Greeting Cards, Undated (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 2)
  - Happy Birthday from Zuke, Undated (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Michelle Crone, Undated (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 4)
  - Postcards, 1979-1984 (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 5)
  - Postcards, 1985-1988 (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 6)
  - Postcards, 1989-1995 (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 7)
  - Postcards, Undated (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 8)
  - Postcard from Pat and Allie, 1982 (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 9)
  - Resumes, 1996; Undated (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 10)
  - Vincentian Senior Prom - Mug, 1976 (Box 30 (3-Personal), Folder 3)
  - Yearbook from the Vincentian Institute - Michelle DeMarco, 1968 (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 11)
  - Yearbook from the Vincentian Institute - Doreen Gaul, 1968 (Box 12 (3-Personal), Folder 12)
- SUNY Albany, 1981-1995, Undated; 4; 1 cubic ft.
  This series contains coursework, notes and notebooks, slides, and a name tag from Michelle Crone's time as a student at the State University of New York at Albany between 1981 and 1986.
  - Administrative Material, 1981-1995 (Box 12 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 13)
  - Class Notebooks, Undated (Box 12 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 14)
  - Class Notes, Assignments, Reports, 1981 (Box 12 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 15)
  - Class Notes, Assignments, Reports, 1981 (Box 12 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 16)
  - Class Notes, Assignments, Reports, 1982 (Box 12 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 17)
  - Class Notes, Assignments, Reports, 1983 (Box 12 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 18)
  - Class Notes, Assignments, Reports, 1984 (Box 12 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 19)
  - Class Notes, Assignments, Reports, 1984 (Box 12 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 20)
  - Class Notes, Assignments, Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 12 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 21)
  - Class Notes, Assignments, Reports, Undated (Box 12 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 22)
  - Film Censorship Project, Undated (Box 13 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 1)
  - Film Class Readings, Undated (Box 13 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 2)
  - Film Class Readings, Undated (Box 13 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 3)
  - Nametag, 1990 (Box 13 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 4)
  - Slides, Undated (Box 13 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 5)
  - Women's Studies Class Material, Undated (Box 13 (4-SUNY Albany), Folder 6)
- Subject Files, 1927-1998, Undated; 5; 12.3 cubic ft.
  This series contains unassociated material organized by subject. This includes event fliers, ephemera, political literature, news clippings, notes, and some photographs.
  - "Affirming Seacoast Community Partnership, Community Scan and Needs Assessment", 1995 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Albany Times-Union, article on Catholic Daughters of America Juniors, 1927 (Oversized 6, Folder 5)
  - Albany Times-Union, 1928 (Oversized 6, Folder 6)
  - Art Prints - 8 images "A Rainbow Path" by Gina Halpen, 1987 (Oversized 6, Folder 10)
  - Article's Newspaper Clippings, 1985; 1988-1995; Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Artwork, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Association of Women's Music and Culture, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Atlanta Gay and Lesbian Community Directory, 1990 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Autograph book given to Donata Stigmate [blank], 1996 (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Banner - "Rochester Women's Action for Peace", Undated (Box 21 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Banner - "Rochester Women Against Violence Against Women", Undated (Box 21 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Banner - "Women" Massachusetts, Undated (Box 21 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Banner - "Plant Roses Not Missiles", Undated (Box 21 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Black ribbon on spool, Undated (Box 34 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Bluefish Productions, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Kate Bornstein, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Bumper Sticker- "Re- Elect Reagan" He Needs the Sleep!, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Business Card Holder, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Buttons, Undated (Box 29 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Buttons, Undated (Box 34 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Buttons, Undated (Box 34 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Buttons, Undated (Box 34 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Califia Community, fliers, notes, 1985; Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Calling All Crones, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Campfest, Leaflets, 1985; 1994 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community Council, Executive Director Search Committee, 1995 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community Council, Minutes, Correspondence, 1988-1989; 1994-1996 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Capital Area G-L Services Directory, 1984 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Capital District Lesbian and Gay Celebration, Leaflet, 1989 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Circle Ceremony, Photographs, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Circle School for Priestesses, 1986 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Citizens for Media Responsibility, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Bill Clinton Inauguration- Metro ticket, 1993 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Collared shirt with purple triangles drawn on it, ca. 1984 (Box 27 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - The Collectives, 1981 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Community Foundation for the Capital Region, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Craftwimmin's Mutual aid Society, Pamphlet, 1988 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - "Crone Hill Flow Chart," drawing of names and connections - on back: "Dykes of Italy" handwritten schedule (22in by 28in), Undated (Flat-file 5, Folder 1)
  - Curing Pill, Undated (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Daisy Dish Rag, 1988; Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Dream On, Ladybrandy, Poetry, 1986 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - D.Y.K.E. (Do You Know Enough?): A Lesbian Game, 1986 (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Eagle Stamp, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - East Coast Lesbian's Festival, Leaflet, 1989 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Ellen Nesbitt Writing Campaign, 1987 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Event Fliers, 1987-1996; Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Event Pamphlets, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Exhibition, Ann Meredith, Spectra Gallery, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Fat Women's Gathering, Program, 1994 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Feminist Archive, Newsletter, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - The Feminist Institute, Leaflet, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Fest Women's Festival, Program, 1991 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Festival of the Mother Goddess, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Film Festivals Programs fliers, 1991-1994 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Fliers, 1985-1989; 1991 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - " For the Lovers on My Rainbow " Jule, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - The Front Page: Serving the Gay and Lesbian Community in North Carolina since 1979, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Gay and Lesbian Antiviolence Project, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Gay Sweatshop Theater Company, 1993 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Girl's Night Out Café, Fliers, 1986; 1991 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Grant Proposals, 1986-1995; Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Green felt bag with paper coasters, Undated (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Green Ribbon - "Behold or Mother Earth the spreading trees!", Undated (Box 33 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Green Ribbon - "Earth horizon and all your people. May your thoughts come to us.", Undated (Box 33 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Grinegan Farm, Newsletters, Correspondence, 1992; 1995 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Gulf Coast, Women's Festival, Program, 1990 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Gypsy Silver Catering Service, 1988-1996 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Handwritten poster, "Dykes of Italy" (22in by 28in), Undated (Flat-file 18, Folder 1)
  - Handwritten poster, "Gypsy Silver Company" (22in by 28in), Undated (Flat-file 17, Folder 1)
  - Handwritten poster, "Sex ed" (22in by 28in), Undated (Flat-file 16, Folder 1)
  - Hanging ornament - two hearts and a circle, Undated (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Hanging rainbow strings, Undated (Box 32 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Hat - Cub Scout hat with buttons, Undated (Box 30 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - "A Heart Connection " Study of Berkshire County Lesbian Community, 1986 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Holding Her Own Fund for Women, 1993 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Imagination Celebration, 1989 (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Index card file in metal box, Undated (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Connie Ingram, Undated (Box 13 (5-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - International Conference on Women's History, 1986 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - International Goddess Festival, Flier, 1994 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Key and keychain, Undated (Box 30 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Knit bag with leather straps, Undated (Box 29 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Knitted circular object, Undated (Box 33 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Larry Kromer, Tori, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - La Ovagenesis- Collections of Women's Writings, 1986 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Large coloring book (17in by 22in), Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 12)
  - Large drawing paper Pad with handwritten notes about peacekeeping and relationship with National Office (18in by 24in), Undated (Flat-file 6, Folder 1)
  - Large green and blue dyed cloth with drawing (50in by 80in), Undated (Box 33 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Large poster of Humphrey Bogart (20in by 28in), Undated (Flat-file 9, Folder 1)
  - Large sign, "Enter Here Revisions Film Festival, New York State Museum Programs" (22in by 18in), Undated (Flat-file 7, Folder 1)
  - Large sign on foam core, "Have you ever been called a bitch?" on back: "Report it to AVP." (20in by 30in), Undated (Flat-file 14, Folder 1)
  - "The Lavender Project: Lesbian Health Care Project ", 1994 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Lesbian Avenger Phone/ Contact Sheet, 1994 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Lesbian Fat Activist Network, Newsletters, 1995 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Literary Exchange Fliers, Leaflets, 1987-1990 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Long Beach Lesbian and Gay Pride, Inc. Unity through Diversity, Production Manager Pass, 1998 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Center posters, Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, Annual Report, 1993 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, " Building a Lesbian Health Center", 1994 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, Correspondence, Memorandum, 1988; 1994-1996 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, Management Retreat [1 of 2], 1994 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, Management Retreat [2 of 2], 1994 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, Plan and Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, Publications, 1987; 1994-1995 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, Women's Night - Access Pass, 1997 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Map of Atlanta, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Metal bells on string with beads, Undated (Box 32 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Metro Cards, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Meeting Poster Notes, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Judith Miller, Letters of Recommendation, 1993-1994 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - "More than a handshake" - map of names and flower drawing, "Susan", "Michelle", Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 1)
  - Movie Poster - Desert Hearts, 1985 (Roll 1, Folder 1)
  - Movie poster for The Maltese Falcon (20in by 28in), Undated (Flat-file 8, Folder 1)
  - Name tag - "Crone, Albany, NY, ECC", Undated (Box 30 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Name tag - Michelle Crone, Undated (Box 30 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Name tag - Michelle Crone from Albany, NY, Undated (Box 30 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Name tag - Hello my name is Tabitha, Undated (Box 30 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - National Black Gay and Lesbian Conference, Program, 1988 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - National Lesbian and Gay Community Funding Partnership, 1996 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - National Women's Music Festival, Fliers, Pamphlets, 1990-1991 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - National Women's Rights Organizing (NWRO), Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - National Women's Studies Association Conference, 1995 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - North American Man-Boy Love Association, 1980-1982; 1985-1986 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Notebook, 1995 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Notebook, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Notepad, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Notepad, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Old Songs Festival, 1982; 1990 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Out Pages- South Florida Community Directory, 1994 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - "Out of the Ashes" White, "Penny Jacqueline", Novel Draft, 1993 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Outpages: The Directory with a sense of community - Frisbee, "I Can See Queerly Now!", Undated (Box 27 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Package of doll toys, "In Vogue, International Ladies[pasted on] Makeup Set," written on back: "Earthquake Preparedness Kit for Ladies", Undated (Box 28 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Pages from large drawing pad attached to poster, "Badge for graffiti," "Stop Rape" (22in by 28in), Undated (Flat-file 12, Folder 1)
  - Painting: "For Michelle in celebration of the mother, Reggae", Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Plastic baby powder air freshener, taped on label: "Personal Air Filtration Unit designed to eliminate urban air pollution", Undated (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Plastic firemen's helmet with rose decals, Undated (Box 28 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Plastic sunglasses, "Baby Eagle", Undated (Box 32 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Plastic sunglasses covered in glitter, Undated (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Poster for West with the Night (15in by 22in), Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 7)
  - Poster - International Festival of Women Artists (17in by 22in), 1980 (Oversized 6, Folder 8)
  - Poster - No Se Prive: es un consejo del colectivo de feministas lesbianas (Do Not Deprive: Council of Lesbian Feminists), Undated (Roll 3, Folder 1)
  - Poster of Carol MacDonald signed "Michelle, this year prude & proud next year S.I.T. if you don't I'll do it, I love you, Carol MacDonald" (18in by 27in), Undated (Flat-file 13, Folder 1)
  - Poster - The Prom You Never Went To (18in by 24in), 1987 (Oversized 6, Folder 11)
  - Poster with photographs and letter to Michelle Crone from Mitzi Swatzell and Robbin Tyler (15in by 19in), Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 2)
  - Power to the People, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Pride and Proud Club, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Project Outline for Artist Archive, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - PWAC Resource Directory, 1994 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Questions for Lesbians, 1995 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Radical Thoughts, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Radio (WRPI's Homo Radio), 1992 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Re-Evaluations Counseling, Harvey Jackins, 1988 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Readings by Oriethyia, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Red ribbon - "My power is uplifted as I sing", Undated (Box 33 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Red ribbon - "Yes! Now we are dancing, Now we move together," [Susan] Griffin, Undated (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - "Report on the High Security Unit for Women, Federal Correctional Institution, Lexington, Kentucky" ACLU, 1987 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Rock crystal, Undated (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Rolled handscroll, Undated (Box 32 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Rolodex, Undated (Box 32 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Rolodex, Undated (Box 32 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - SAGE (Senior Action in a Gay Environment), 1988; Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - The Saratogan, article and photo of Amelia Earhart, 1935 (Oversized 6, Folder 4)
  - Scholastic, 1937 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Sculpture - "To Tab, Happy Solstice", 1993 (Box 29 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Sisterfire Festival, Program, 1987 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Shake off the patriarchy tree, hand drawn poster (22in by 28in), Undated (Flat-file 15, Folder 1)
  - Sign: "Area Seeded Please Stay Off, Field Open June 1" (12in by 18in), Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 3)
  - Silver cross in jewelry box, Undated (Box 34 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Small bottle with white substance, attached printed label: "New and Improved Instantawater by Chia Pet, Inc., Undated (Box 34 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Small mirror with religious icon on back, Undated (Box 30 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Small plastic book with cross, Undated (Box 34 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Spectrum Conference, 1986 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - State University of New York at Albany, Mentor Program, Correspondence, 1989; 1991 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - "Stop Homophobia" stop sign poster (22in by 23in), Undated (Flat-file 11, Folder 1)
  - "Stop Rape" stop sign poster (22in by 23in), Undated (Flat-file 10, Folder 1)
  - Spinsterhaven, 1991-1992 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Sydney Gay and Lesbian Mardi- Gras. Program, 1990 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Sydney Lesbian Festival, Program, 1991 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - T-shirt - Australia, Sydney Gay & Lesbian Mardi Gras, 1995 (Box 28 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - T-shirt - Che Guevara portrait, ¡Hasta la victoria siempre! Alianzade la Juventud Socialista" (Always to Victory! Alliance of Socialist Youth), Undated (Box 28 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - T-shirt - Lea DeLaria Queer Brat, Undated (Box 27 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - T-shirt - Never Again! yer girlfriend, Undated (Box 27 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - T-shirt - Running Strong for American Indian Youth, Winner's Circle, 1994 (Box 27 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - T-shirt - Slo Life, San Luis Obispo, California, Undated (Box 27 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - T-shirt - "To my Big Brother Michelle, Cunt, Tits, Pussy, Wet, Hot, Suckin & Fuckin, Lia, Rita. P.S. Prude and Proud, 1990 (Box 22 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - T-shirt - The Transsexual Menace, New York City, Undated (Box 28 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - T-shirt - "Yabba Dabba Dykes", Undated (Box 27 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - T-shirt - You've come a long way baby, Undated (Box 27 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)